{"data":[{"question":"She is _____ a boat.","a":"make","b":"doing","c":"do","d":"making","answer":"4","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating \n- Be + V_ing: Present continuous tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't ______ that exercise!","a":"do","b":"have","c":"make","d":"did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- 'Do' is often used when referring to work of any kind\n- Don't + infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They are _____ too much noise.","a":"doing","b":"make","c":"making","d":"to do","answer":"3","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating \n- Be + V_ing: Continuous tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you _____ the tea yet?","a":"done","b":"made","c":"did","d":"make","answer":"2","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating \n- Because this is present perfect tense: make - made","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"My sister is ______ nothing this morning.","a":"doing","b":"making","c":"done","d":"made","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use the verb 'do' when speaking about things in general: to describe an action without saying exactly what the action is. \n- This form is often used with the words 'something, nothing, anything, everything, etc \n- Be + V_ing: continous tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm going to ______ some coffee.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"2","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating \n- Going to + Verb Infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ me a good favor last year.","a":"do","b":"made","c":"make","d":"did","answer":"4","explain":"\n- There are a number of standard expressions that take the verb 'do' ;For example: Do a favor; do business... \n- \"Did\" is past tense of \"Do\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We aren't going to ______ anything.","a":"do","b":"having","c":"make","d":"doing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use the verb 'do' when speaking about things in general: to describe an action without saying exactly what the action is. \n- This form is often used with the words 'something, nothing, anything, everything, etc \n- Going to + Verb Infinitive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't _____ a noise!","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Structure: make a noise.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you _____ dinner yet?","a":"make","b":"do","c":"made","d":"done","answer":"3","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating \n- This is present continuous tense: Make- made","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}